<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>UAV Research Centre</title>
    <link>/</link>
      <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>UAV Research Centre</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 21:54:17 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/images/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>UAV Research Centre</title>
      <link>/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using multiangular information for accurate acquisition of leaf area and chlorophyll content</title>
      <link>/project/bof-startup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 21:54:17 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/bof-startup/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With UAV snapshot cameras, the same area is observed manifold and under a variety of different viewing angles. The standard UAV image processing software only use one of these observations to create the orthophotos – all other observations are discarded. Yet, these multi-angular data actually reveal very relevant information on canopy properties. In this project, we use the full multi-angular observation to generate maps of leaf area and chlorophyll content, two parameters of immediate use for precision agriculture applications.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bof Startup</title>
      <link>/projects/bof-startup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 21:53:52 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>/projects/bof-startup/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COMP4DRONES</title>
      <link>/project/comp-4-drones/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 11:27:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/comp-4-drones/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;COMP4DRONES is an ECSEL JU project coordinated by Indra that brings together a consortium of 50 partners with the aim of providing a framework of key enabling technologies for safe and autonomous drones. It brings to bear a holistically designed ecosystem from application to electronic components, realized as a tightly integrated multi-vendor and compositional UAV embedded architecture solution and a tool chain complementing the compositional architecture principles.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ANALYST PV</title>
      <link>/project/analyst-pv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 11:19:54 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/analyst-pv/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;ANALYST PV is an imec.icon research project funded by imec, Innoviris and Agentschap Innoveren &amp;amp; Ondernemen. It started on 01.10.2019 and is set to run until 30.09.2021.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ANALYST PV project will develop a fault diagnosis framework that relies on IoT sensors, AI-enabled root cause analysis and automatic image analysis. The ultimate goal is to optimize photovoltaic asset management and performance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our work in the project consists of developing image processing techniques to detect and classify anomalies that occur on solar panels including bypass substrings, junction box issues, diode issues, string issues and potential induced defects (PID). We also aim at improving structure from motion algorithms in a way that they can better deal with the repetitive patterns present in UAV imagery of PV power plants.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
